icorrect.com 2013-12-26

# ICorrect Privacy Policy | ICorrect - The Universal Website for Corrections

ICorrect takes the privacy of its users seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users while providing a personalized and valuable service. This Privacy Policy explains the data processing practices of ICorrect. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us at: [enquiries@icorrect.com](mailto:enquiries@icorrect.com)

### Information collected

Personal information is collected by ICorrect from you through the registration forms and every time you e-mail us your details. We also collect information automatically about your visit to our site. The information obtained in this way, which includes demographic data and browsing patterns, is only used in aggregate form. 

### Use and Disclosure of personal information

We process personal information collected via ICorrect.com for the purposes of: 
  * providing a personalized service
  * conducting market research surveys
  * running news scans to track stories concerning you in the public domain
  * providing you with information about services we offer

We also use information in aggregate form (so that no individual user is identified): 
  * to build up marketing profiles
  * to aid strategic development
  * to audit usage of the site

### Use of cookies

We use "cookies" to identify you when you visit the ICorrect site and to build up a demographic profile. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser. Our use of cookies also allows registered users to be presented with a personalized version of the site. 

### Internet-based transfers

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing the ICorrect site and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way. If you require any more assistance on the privacy policies at ICorrect, please e-mail us at: [enquiries@icorrect.com](mailto:enquiries@icorrect.com)
